[AXA
---

36.190

( +0.14%)](https://www.axa.com/en/investor/axa-share-performances#anchor=market-data&tab=share-performance)

* About Us
* Commitments
* News
* Press
* Investors
* Careers

Open search form

Privacy Policy
==============

AXA Group respects your privacy and ensures that all the personal data it handles is processed in accordance with best confidentiality practices and the applicable laws on data protection, and notably the European Union General Data Protection Regulation n°2016/679 (GDPR).

AXA Group is committed to adapting the information provided to the target audience. Therefore, you will find below, available at any time and downloadable, Privacy Policies centralizing and detailing all the processing that concerns you according to the relationship you have with the AXA Group.

If you wish to know more about the processing of your personal data and you are:

* A visitor to the axa.com website, please [click here](https://www-axa-com.cdn.axa-contento-118412.eu/www-axa-com/867533c9-d2ea-4356-b4de-8f2e03c5833c_axa_privacypolicy_feb2024_va.pdf)
* A whistleblower (or if you are the subject of an alert or are concerned by an alert), please [click here](https://www-axa-com.cdn.axa-contento-118412.eu/www-axa-com/d829b585-f19a-4f95-88a8-153c14961d4a_axa_whistleblowing_feb2024_va.pdf)
* A shareholder, i.e., you invest in AXA - whether you are a member of the Shareholders' Circle (to learn more about the Shareholders' Circle, [click here](https://www.axa.com/en/investor/shareholders-circle)), please [click here](https://www-axa-com.cdn.axa-contento-118412.eu/www-axa-com/99498ffe-73db-48c8-ab7a-bb2d68de560e_axa_shareholders_feb2024_va.pdf)
* A client or prospect of the local entities of the AXA Group, please [click here](https://www-axa-com.cdn.axa-contento-118412.eu/www-axa-com/f3f0d4a8-d157-474c-9f58-c7cb78cd92f8_axa_customers_feb2024_va.pdf)
* An Internet user and you follow the AXA Group on its networks or its various websites, please [click here](https://www-axa-com.cdn.axa-contento-118412.eu/www-axa-com/52c78cab-ca88-4b6a-a818-81f470de9004_axa_internetusers_feb2024_va.pdf)
* A service provider or consultant in relation with GIE AXA, AXA SA, GIE AXA Université or AXA Group Operations, please [click here](https://www-axa-com.cdn.axa-contento-118412.eu/www-axa-com/f9683bba-247b-44b7-88a8-84c0a274afdf_axa_consultants_feb2024_va.pdf)

The identity of the data controllers (i.e., they determine the purposes and means of the processing of your information), is indicated in the Privacy Policies available above.

However, you are informed that GIE AXA, an Economic Interest Grouping, organized under French laws, having its registered office at 23 Avenue Matignon, 75008 Paris, registered with the Registry of Commerce and Companies of Paris under number 333 491 066, acts as an independent data controller in the context of the processing of your personal data.

In some cases, GIE AXA and AXA SA (excluding these subsidiaries) a Société Anonyme, organized under French laws, having its registered office at 25 Avenue Matignon, 75008 Paris, registered with the Registry of Commerce and Companies of Paris under number 572 093 920, act as joint data controllers in the context of the processing of your personal data (i.e., they jointly determine the purposes and means of the processing of your information).

As a reminder, and as indicated in the Privacy Policies available above, in accordance with the French Informatique et Libertés law n° 78-17 of 6 January 1978 and the GDPR, you have the right to:

* Access to your personal data, you have the right to request access to the personal data we process about you, and to obtain a copy of that data
* Rectify your personal data, you have the right to ask AXA to rectify or complete the personal data that we process about you that are inaccurate, incomplete, or not up to date
* Request the limitation of the processing of your personal data, you have the right to ask AXA to limit the processing of your personal data. This means that we may simply keep your data but may not process or use it in any other way,
* Decide what happens to your personal data after your death, you have the right to give AXA instructions as to how your personal data should be used after your death

Based on the legal basis for the processing of your personal data, you have also the right to:

* Request the deletion of your personal data, you have the right to ask AXA to delete your personal data, except where the processing is based on the performance of a legal obligation of the data controllers
* Right to portability of your personal data, you have the right to receive the personal data you have provided to us in a suitable format and have the right to transfer that data to another data controller without us interfering but only where the processing is based on your consent or on the execution of a contract
* Withdraw your consent at any time by contacting the following address [privacy@axa.com](mailto:privacy@axa.com), but only where the processing of your personal data is based on your consent

Where the processing of your data is based on AXA Group's legitimate interests, you also have the right to:

* Object at any time to the processing of your personal data, unless the data controllers can demonstrate the need for further processing or where such data is necessary for the establishment, exercise, or defense of legal claims
* Request information on the balancing test by contacting the following address: [privacy@axa.com](mailto:privacy@axa.com)

You can exercise these rights by contacting [privacy@axa.com](mailto:privacy@axa.com) or by sending a letter to the following addresses: 23 avenue Matignon, 75008, Paris for GIE AXA or 25 avenue Matignon, 75008, Paris for AXA SA.

The data controllers may ask you for additional information to confirm your identity and/or to assist data controllers to locate the data you are seeking.

You are informed of your right to raise concerns about how your personal data is being processed with a competent supervisory authority, in particular in the Member State of your habitual residence, place of work or place where you think an alleged infringement to your rights occurred.

In France, the data protection authority is the Commission Nationale de l'Informatique et des Libertés, or CNIL whose postal address is 3 place de Fontenoy - TSA 80715 – 75334 Paris CEDEX 07. Its website is accessible here: [https://www.cnil.fr/](https://www.cnil.fr/).

Date of last update: January 24, 2024

DIRECT ACCESS

DATA PROTECTION

* Cookie Management

ACCESSIBILITY

FOLLOW US

English

/[Français](https://www.axa.com/fr/page/politique-de-protection-des-donnees-a-caractere-personnel)

[Legal information and terms of use](https://www.axa.com/en/about-us/Legal-Information) © 2024 AXA All Rights Reserved
